McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus
1871-1907
1895-1905
Manuscripts Division
McCaddon, Joseph T.
TC040
85 boxes
9 folders
14 items
The McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus consists of correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, and other material collected by business manager Joseph T. McCaddon prior to the 1907 merger of the circus with Ringling Bros.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
For preservation reasons, original analog and digital media may not be read or played back in the reading room. Users may visually inspect physical media but may not remove it from its enclosure. All analog audiovisual media must be digitized to preservation-quality standards prior to use. Audiovisual digitization requests are processed by an approved third-party vendor. Please note, the transfer time required can be as little as several weeks to as long as several months and there may be financial costs associated with the process. Requests should be directed through the Ask Us Form.
Scope and Contents
Consists of the working papers of the Barnum and Bailey partnership prior to its merger with Ringling Bros. in 1907. In addition to correspondence, scrapbooks, posters, couriers, parade, costume and wagon designs, music, and memorabilia collected by Joseph T. McCaddon, who was the business manager of the circus at the turn of the century, there are hundreds of photographs documenting the American circus of the 19th and 20th centuries.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was a gift to the Library by the McCaddon family in 1941. Additions were purchased at auction in July 1978.
Appraisal
No appraisal information is available.
Content Warning
The McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus contains harmful and offensive descriptions of people that includes racist, colonialist, ableist, and otherwise dehumanizing language. Some of the description is original to the donor and/or the creator, and in these instances of creator- and donor-supplied titles, description may be retained to convey contextual/historical information of the materials. However, the collection is a candidate for ongoing reparative description work that can address cases in which a librarian or archivist may have supplied harmful descriptive language. We hope that researchers will engage in a dialogue with staff about issues in the collection and changes that could help.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The glass-plate negatives require special handling in the reading room.
McCaddon, Joseph T.
Biographical / Historical
Joseph T. McCaddon was born on January 31, 1859, in Beverly, Washington County, Ohio. McCaddon began his career with the circus as manager of the Adam Forepaugh Circus. Later, as James A. Bailey's brother-in-law and business manager of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, he represented Bailey in many business matters, including correspondence with William F. Cody ("Buffalo Bill") regarding the acquisition of his Wild West Show.
[1824] John Robinson Circus formed
1867 Adam Forepaugh Circus formed
1871 P. T. Barnum begins "P.T. Barnum's Museum, Menagerie, & Circus" in Brooklyn, N.Y.
1873 James A. Bailey buys interest in Hemmings and Cooper's Circus from James E. Cooper, changes name to Cooper and Bailey Circus.
1875 Sells Bros. Circus formed
1879-80 Bailey, along with Cooper and James L. Hutchinson, purchases show owned by Seth B. Howes, forming Howes' Great London Circus and Sanger's Royal British Menagerie and Cooper & Bailey's International Allied Shows
1881 Cooper retires; Bailey and Hutchinson form partnership with Barnum, creating the Barnum and London Circus.
1883 Buffalo Bill's Wild West founded
1884 The Ringling Brothers establish their circus.
1885 Bailey sells his interest in the circus to Cooper and W. W. Cole.
1888 Barnum and Bailey begin sole partnership, forming the "Barnum and Bailey Circus."
1890 Bailey and Cooper buy Adam Forepaugh Circus.
1891 Barnum dies; Bailey assumes full ownership of Barnum and Bailey Circus.
1894 Bailey buys a controlling interest in Buffalo Bill's Wild West.
1896 Bailey joins with W. W. Cole and two of the Sells Brothers; Sells Bros. Circus becomes Adam Forepaugh and Sells Bros. Circus
1897-1902 5-year Barnum and Bailey European Tour. Ringling Bros. Circus becomes dominant American Circus.
1898 Ringling Bros. begin to lease John Robinson Circus.
1905 Bailey acquires full ownership of Adam Forepaugh and Sells Bros. Circus, sells half interest in it to the Ringling Bros.
1906 Bailey dies; Ringling Brothers buy remaining share of Forepaugh-Sells Circus from Bailey's widow.
1907 Ringling Brothers purchase "Barnum and Bailey Circus" (shows remain separate).
1919 "Ringling Brothers Circus" combined with "Barnum and Bailey Circus" to create "Ringling Brothers and Barnum & Bailey Circus"
1929 Ringling Brothers purchase American Circus (which consisted of Sells-Floto, Al G. Barnes, Sparks, Hagenbeck-Wallace, and John Robinson Circuses).
1956 Ringling Brothers and Barnum & Bailey Circus gives last big top performance.
1957 Irvin Feld purchases "Ringling Brothers and Barnum & Bailey Circus" and transforms it into an indoor show.
Circus -- United States -- History -- Sources.; Circus -- United States -- Photographs.; Circus animals -- United States.; Circus owners -- United States.; Circus performers -- United States.; Circus performers -- United States -- Costume.; Circus trains -- United States.; Circus wagons -- United States.; Costume designers -- United States -- Drawings.; Correspondence.; Photographs.; Posters.; Scrapbooks.; Barnum and Bailey
- Series 1: Photographs, 1854-1903; 16 boxes; 8 items
  Scope and Contents
  Consists of photographs of exotica, performers, animal acts, "freaks," and equipment used by the circus.
  Arrangement
  Arranged by subject of photograph.
  Content Warning
  Many of the photographs in this series contain dehumanizing and harmful descriptions using racist, colonialist, and ableist language. In the majority of cases, the descriptions of people have been transcribed from the photographs themselves. Some of the photographs have been stamped with titles (likely by the original photographic studio); other titles are handwritten. In cases where photographs have no title, descriptions derive from a typewritten inventory of the collection that may have been provided by the donor, or may have been created by an archivist.
  - Exotica, 1878-1900 November; 4 boxes
    - Two men of "Todas Indians", or the lost children of Israel. (two different shots, duplicates), dates not examined; 4 items (Box 1, Item 1-4)
    - Bushman, native of Australia, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 5)
    - Two Bushwomen and child, natives of Australia, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 6)
    - Band of eight Nubians, natives of Soudan, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 7)
    - Zulu Warriors: three men, princess, child, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 8)
    - Samoan Warrior, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 9)
    - Princess Silaulii Iviletufuga of Samoa, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 10)
    - Princess Silaulii of Samoa, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Native warrior of unidentified tribe, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 12)
    - Three Afghan Warriors, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 13)
    - Two Afghan Warriors, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 1, Item 14-15)
    - Two Singalese males, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 1, Item 16-17)
    - Two Japanese Wrestlers, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 18)
    - Unidentified Oriental Man with long pigtail, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 19)
    - Group of four unidentified natives, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 20)
    - Kling man and child, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 21)
    - Series of Singalese masked devil dancers, undated; 6 items (Box 1, Item 22-27)
      #24 shows Kandyan dancers in "Jes" ritual clothing.
    - Mr. Ali Bendeb from Desi "Chief Arabs" with two unidentified females, one unidentified male (fighting), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 28)
      See nos. 37, 38, 67-71.
    - High caste "Hindoos" (Hindus), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 30)
    - Unidentified Indian woman in sari and jewelry, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 31)
    - Unidentified Indian woman in sari and jewelry, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 32)
    - Unidentified group of four Indians with Eastern musical instruments, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 33)
    - Genuine Hindoo Nautch Dancers (3), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 34)
    - Two unidentified male knife and spear artists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 35)
    - Singhalese man and child in ox-drawn cart, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 36)
    - Mr. Ali Bendeb from Desi "Chief Arabs" with two unidentified females and one unidentified male, playing instruments and dancing, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 1, Item 37-38)
      See nos. 28, 29, 67-71.
    - Ali Bendeb with unidentified female, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 1, Item 39-40)
    - Ali Bendeb with two men, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 40a)
    - Ali Bendeb with two women, one man, and a baby, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 41)
    - Two unidentified Turks with swords, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 42)
    - Unidentified Procession, including elephants led by drummers, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 43)
    - Elephant, with native rider, lifting wood beam, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 44)
    - Unidentified man in Eastern dress, sitting in a rickshaw pulled by a coolie, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 45)
    - American Indians, "Red Cloud" and "Spotted Tail" with C.P. Jordan, 1882; 1 item (Box 1, Item 46)
    - Siamese warrior, two youths, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 47)
    - Unidentified Middle-Eastern man, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 48)
    - Unidentified Middle-Eastern woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 49)
    - Unidentified Middle-Eastern woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 50)
    - Unidentified man, woman, and child, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 51)
    - Unidentified man and woman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 52)
    - Unidentified man and woman, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 53)
    - Unidentified Indian or Ceylonese girl, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 54)
    - Unidentified man and woman, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 55)
    - Unidentified man and woman, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 55a)
    - Unidentified man, woman, and child, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 56)
    - Unidentified man, woman, and boy, Ceylonese, undated; 1 item (Box 1, Item 57)
    - Unidentified man and woman, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 58)
    - Unidentified man, woman, and child, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 59)
    - Unidentified youths with woman nursing child, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 60)
    - Six musicians, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 61)
    - Male artisan with rack and embroidery, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 1, Item 62-63)
    - Two men with miniature sailboats, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 64)
    - Group photo of Indian and Ceylonese inhabitants of Indian Village, International Exhibition (imported by William Cross, naturalist), Liverpool, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 65)
      See nos. 48-64 for other photos of same.
    - Group of eight unidentified Arabs, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 1, Item 66)
    - Ali Bendeb, "Great Sheik of Bedouin Arabs" plus two unidentified men; Sultana and Nanc, Arab women, dates not examined; 4 items (Box 1, Item 67-70)
      See nos. 28, 29, 37, 38.
    - Ali Bendeb, "Great Sheik of Bedouin Arabs" plus two unidentified men; Sultana and Nanc, Arab women, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 71)
    - Unidentified men with weapons on horse (Turk?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 72)
    - Male native (Moroccan?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 73)
    - Group of eight Australian aborigines, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 74)
    - Singhalese man with Barnum midget, Ceylon Exhibition, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 75)
    - Unidentified man and woman, Australian aborigines, New Guinea natives, or Central Africans, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 2, Item 76-77)
    - Two male Central African pygmies, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 2, Item 78-79)
    - Female midget with child, Indian or Ceylonese, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 2, Item 80-81)
    - Two men, Australian aborigines or New Guinea natives, dates not examined; 5 items (Box 2, Item 82-85, Item 85a)
    - Two women, Australian aborigines or New Guinea natives, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 2, Item 86-87)
    - Three women and one child, Australian aborigines or New Guinea natives, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 2, Item 88-89)
    - Elephants bearing natives and an Englishman, India, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 90)
    - Three Japanese female musicians, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 91)
    - Photo of vichy - Le Casino, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 92)
    - Chalons - Le Cirque, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 93)
    - Bohemian Industrial Museum, Prague, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 94)
    - Barnum and Baileys Winter Home, 1900 November, Wien I, Rotunde, 1 item (Box 2, Item 95)
    - "Palais Imperial" (Summer residence) of Dom Pedro II Petropolis, Brazil, 1878; 1 item (Box 2, Item 96)
    - General view of Rio de Janeiro, harbor entrance, with Sugar Loaf Mountain in background (oversize), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 16, Item 97)
    - South Sea Island Joe, Curio Shop, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 98)
    - Arab musician with trained bear, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 99)
    - Arab snake charmer, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 100)
    - Entrance to Suez Canal, Port Saud, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 101)
    - Arab "Fakir" musician with monkey and burro, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 102)
    - Arab musicians (3) - Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 102a)
    - Two female Arabs making bread, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 103)
    - Female Arab dancer, Egypt, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 2, Item 104)
    - Photos of Albert Memorial, London, dates not examined; 18 items (Box 2, Item 105-122)
    - Photos of Albert Memorial, London, dates not examined; 80 items (Box 3, Item 123-202)
      [123 missing 6/04]
    - Crew races at Cambridge, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 3, Item 203-204)
  - Performers I, 1871-1898; 3 boxes
    - Red Cross nurse in "The Mahdi", or "For the Victoria Cross.", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Barnum T. Bailey, Olympia, London, 1897-1898 season, 1 item (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Peace Council between Sioux and Chippewa Indians. Buffalo, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Bill's Wild West Show; Ashland, Wis, 1896 September 11; 1 item (Box 4, Item 2)
    - "The Shoits", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 3)
    - Tom Elliott of "The Elliotts", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Lizzie L. Sturgeon, pedal pianist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 5)
    - Dolly Sharpe Lang, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 6)
    - Mlle. Arnette, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 7)
    - Sam Lang, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 8)
    - Mlle. Arnette, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 9)
    - Sam Lang, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 10)
    - Akimoto's Royal Japanese Troupe, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 11)
    - "Pawnee Bill", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 12)
    - "Pearl and Ruby", children of "Nelline" - Golden-Haired Albino, five and nine years old, Minneapolis, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 13)
    - High Stilts, Champion Stilt-Walker in Europe, J. Rossini, in character of "Beadle" in Dick Turpin. Taken for five years with Cinnett's Olympia, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 14)
    - Unidentified y. male, bust, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 15)
    - High Stilts, Champion Stilt-Walker in Europe, J. Rossini, character of "Ally Sloper," Cinnett's Olympia, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 16)
    - Karoly Ordey of "The Ordeys Hungarian Jugglers", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 17)
      See no. 151.
    - Demonio; forward bender, contortionist, 1884-1893; 1 item (Box 4, Item 18)
    - The Great Demonio, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 19)
    - Unidentified strong man; W.L., arms extended, with chains and rings, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 20)
    - Unidentified strong man; W.L. dressed in animal skins, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 21)
    - Unidentified strong man; H.L., with moustache, arms crossed, dressed in animal skins and medals, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 22)
    - Andy Sweeney, strong man; W.L., chains wrapped around hands, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 23)
    - Mlle. Cassinora, Tattooed Lady; Steuben Co., N.Y., dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 24)
    - Holly Harding (Circassian with teased hair), undated; 1 item (Box 4, Item 25)
    - Unidentified woman (Holly Harding?) and child (Circassian with teased hair), beside a table bearing fruit and flower displays, undated; 1 item (Box 4, Item 26)
    - Zola Zolera (Circassian with teased hair), with live snake twined around arms, undated; 1 item (Box 4, Item 27)
      See Box 9.
    - Unidentified girl, W.L., in ballet dress, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 28)
    - Unidentified woman in toreador costume, dates not examined; 3 items (Box 4, Item 29-31)
    - W. Hickler, strong man, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 32)
    - The Great Ceado, gymnast and aerial performer, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 33)
    - Miss Blanche Edwards, aerialist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 34)
    - Capt. Bogardus, Champion Rifle Shot of the World. Adam Forepaugh Shows, 1892; 1 item (Box 4, Item 35)
    - Barnello, man with the breath of fire, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 36)
      See no. 157.
    - Lena Blatt, The Water Lily, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 37)
    - Andy Sweeney, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 38)
      See no. 23.
    - "Krao", "Farini's Missing Link," hirsute, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 39)
      [missing 1/85]
    - Unidentified male juggler, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 40)
    - Edna Bartholdi, gymnast, contortionist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 41)
    - Edna Bartholdi, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 42)
    - G. Arcaris and sister, Spanish, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 43)
    - Albion Family; William, Ettie, Willie, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 44)
    - Will Oxford, Champion English Rider and Jockey, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 45)
    - Duplicate Will Oxford, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 46)
    - Unidentified woman, seated with book, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 47)
    - Emma Lake (Robinson), daughter of Bill Lake, Circus proprietor, equestrienne, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 48)
    - "The Mecca Brothers" in "The Heather Step", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 49)
    - "The Mecca Brothers" in "The Heather Step", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 4, Item 50)
    - Bertre, St. Louis, Mo., 1883; 1 item (Box 5, Item 51)
    - H.&L.M. D'Esta, Living Pictures, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 52)
    - Bingham, ventriloquist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 53)
    - Etta, Great Mind Reader. N- Circus, 1877; 1 item (Box 5, Item 54)
    - J.R. Kaldenburg, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 55)
    - "The Clignots", dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 56)
    - Miss Blanche Edwards, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 57)
    - Unidentified man in top hat, with unidentified woman in gypsy dress, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 58)
    - Unidentified woman in ethnic dress with ballet slippers, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 59)
    - Alfred Riaawelli, Circus Drexler & Lobe, Nuremberg, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 60)
    - Hanlon-Volters, midgets, aerialists, gymnasts. (John Ryan, Williams O'Meara, Patrick Cormady), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 61)
    - Unidentified balancer, in costume, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 62)
    - Diegrist Children (3), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 63)
    - Two unidentified children (contortionists?), dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 64)
    - "Master Lee" child in costume, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 5, Item 65-66)
    - "Baron & Oscar, et ses Cochons Savants", animal trainer and pig, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 67)
    - Nicholas, child contortionist, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 68)
    - George Davenport, Dutch comedian, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 69)
    - Madame Valeska, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 70)
    - I. Alfleming, Inventor of wire writing, with display, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 71)
    - Unidentified man, W.L., in formal dress, with top hat, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 72)
    - Unidentified youth in Spanish attire, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 73)
    - Bust of unidentified woman in gypsy cap, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 74)
    - Bust of unidentified woman in gypsy cap with coins and bead necklace, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 75)
    - Polly and Kate Elliott, bicyclists, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 76)
    - Unidentified trio in armour, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 77)
    - Prof. C.P. Blatt, Champion Man Fish of the World, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 78)
    - Mrs. Fritz, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 79)
    - Unidentified woman in bracelets, beads, mantilla, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 80)
    - Unidentified man in woman's clothing with baby, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 81)
    - Leonard Kleeb, player of harmonica, guitar, percussion, and, own invention, accordophon. West Wareham, MA., dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 82)
    - G. Arcaris and sister, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 83)
      See no. 52.
    - Marque Family (8), musical wonders, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 84)
    - Unidentified girl with violin, standing on large ball, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 85)
    - Matthews Bros., violinists, comedians, rifle, rope, and sword performers, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 5, Item 86-87)
    - Samarjian, Turkish swordsman, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 88)
    - Rawson & June, spear and boomerang throwers, undated; 2 items (Box 5, Item 89-90)
    - Farm and home of Rawson & June, boomerang throwers, undated; 1 item (Box 5, Item 91)
    - Unidentified couple; fencers, dagger artists, dates not examined; 2 items (Box 5, Item 92-93)
    - Sig. & Mlle Cassinora, Mexican Impalement Act, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 94)
      See no. 24.
    - Unidentified impalement act, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 95)
    - W.D. Amernt (Mexican Billy), rifle shot, dates not examined; 1 item (Box 5, Item 96)